<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sighisoara City</string>
    <!-- Hotels fragment -->
    <string name="hotel_1_name">DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel Sighisoara - Cavaler</string>
    <string name="hotel_1_description">Located 200 m from the Sighișoara Citadel, listed as a World
        Heritage Site by the UNESCO, DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel Sighisoara - Cavaler offers free
        access to a spa featuring a Finnish sauna, a steam bath, and an indoor pool.
        \nAll the stylish, air-conditioned rooms provide a minibar and a flat-screen TV.
        The bathrooms come with all toiletries. Some of DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel Sighisoara -
        Cavaler’s rooms and suites have interior stairs.</string>
    <string name="hotel_1_website">http://www.hiltonhotels.com/ro_RO/romania/doubletree-by-
        hilton-hotel-sighisoara-cavaler/</string>

    <string name="hotel_2_name">Pension Casa Saseasca</string>
    <string name="hotel_2_description">Situated within the UNESCO-protected Sighişoara Citadel, the
        Pension Casa Saseasca occupies a historic building dating back to the 18th century.
        Free WiFi is available.\nAll rooms feature hand-made traditional furniture and have a
        private bathroom.</string>
    <string name="hotel_2_website">http://www.casasaseasca.com</string>

    <string name="hotel_3_name">Hotel Korona</string>
    <string name="hotel_3_description">
        Offering an on-site restaurant, Hotel Korona is situated at the foot of the Mediaeval Citadel
        of Sighisoara, a 5-minute walk from the commercial and historic centre.
        It offers spacious accommodation with free WiFi.
    </string>
    <string name="hotel_3_website">www.hotelkorona.ro</string>

    <string name="hotel_4_name">Hotel Casa Wagner</string>
    <string name="hotel_4_description">
       Casa Wagner welcomes you in an unique historic setting on the main square of the
        UNESCO-protected old town of Sighisoara and offers you well-equipped, individually
        decorated rooms and fine cuisine.
        \nFrom the moment you enter the hotel rooms or you see the vaulted ceiling of the restaurant or the
        wine cellar, you will be surrounded by a unique historic ambience.
    </string>
    <string name="hotel_4_website">www.casa-wagner.com</string>

    <string name="hotel_5_name">Taschler Haus</string>
    <string name="hotel_5_description">Taschler Haus offers accommodation in Sighişoara,
        only 150 m away from the renown 14th-century Clock Tower. Free WiFi is available throughout
        the property.\nThe rooms are fitted with a flat-screen TV and a private bathroom.
        For your comfort, you will find free toiletries and a hairdryer. Some units feature a
        seating area to relax in after a busy day, and a safe is available in every unit.
    </string>
    <string name="hotel_5_website">http://taschlerhaus.com/</string>

    <!-- Restaurants fragment -->
    <string name="restaurant_1_name">Joseph T. Restaurant &amp; Wine Bar</string>
    <string name="restaurant_1_description">Romanian and international cuisine served in a
        elegant setting. Best Romanian wine selection in Transylvania.
    </string>
    <string name="restaurant_1_website">""</string>

    <string name="restaurant_2_name">Georgius Krauss House</string>
    <string name="restaurant_2_description">
        In the menu list are found many dishes, carefully chosen, for flavor, finesse and especially for all tastes.
        \nThe kitchen of our house is lead by Chef Florin Mihalache, who prepares well documented plates,
        whether it's about fine ingredients, or that we have a traditional recipe in front of us,
        EVERY DISH HAS IT'S OWN STORY.
    </string>
    <string name="restaurant_2_website">www.casakrauss.ro</string>

    <string name="restaurant_3_name">Gasthaus Alte Post</string>
    <string name="restaurant_3_description">
       "The restaurant has mainly traditional food from local cuisine (hungarian and romanian)"
    </string>
    <string name="restaurant_3_website">www.gasthaus-altepost.ro</string>

    <string name="restaurant_4_name">Cositorarului House</string>
    <string name="restaurant_4_description"></string>
    <string name="restaurant_4_website">www.casa-cositorarului.ro</string>


    <string name="restaurant_5_name">Ferdinand House</string>
    <string name="restaurant_5_description"></string>
    <string name="restaurant_5_website">www.casa-ferdinand.ro</string>

    <!-- Cultural -->
    <string name="cultural_1_name">Clock Tower</string>
    <string name="cultural_1_description">The Clock Tower of Sighișoara is the main entry point to
        the citadel, opposite guarded by Taylor\'s Tower. With its 64 meters of height, the tower
        is visible from almost every corner of the city from Mures County, its purpose was to defend
        the main gate of the citadel and also served as the town hall until 1556. Now It's considered
        one of the most expressive clock tower in the whole Transylvania.</string>
    <string name="cultural_1_website">http://sighisoaraonline.com</string>

    <string name="cultural_2_name">Covered Stairs</string>
    <string name="cultural_2_description">This is an old wood and stone staircase with a wooden
        roof along the whole span. It has 175 wood steps and is was build in 1642 with the aim to
        make easier access for school students to reach the Hill School.</string>
    <string name="cultural_2_website">http://sighisoaraonline.com</string>


    <string name="cultural_3_name">Church on the Hill</string>
    <string name="cultural_3_description">The Church on the Hill is an architecturally significant
        church located in Sighişoara, Mureș County in Romania.This church is the most important
        monument of religious architecture in Sighisoara and is one of the great churches of
        Transylvania, being the third largest.</string>
    <string name="cultural_3_website">http://sighisoaraonline.com</string>


    <string name="cultural_4_name">Historic Centre of Sighișoara</string>
    <string name="cultural_4_description">The Historic Centre of Sighișoara is the old historic
        center of the town of Sighișoara,Romania, built in the 12th century by Saxon colonists
        under the Latin name Castrum Sex. It is an inhabited medieval citadel that, in 1999,
        was designated a UNESCO World Heritage Site for its 850-year-old testament to the history
        and culture of the Transylvanian Saxons.</string>
    <string name="cultural_4_website">http://sighisoaraonline.com</string>

    <string name="cultural_5_name">Sighișoara Medieval Festival</string>
    <string name="cultural_5_description">Sighişoara Medieval Festival or Festivalul Sighişoara
        Medievală is a Romanian festival held on the last weekend of July in Sighişoara, Romania.</string>
    <string name="cultural_5_website">http://sighisoaraonline.com</string>

    <!-- Nightlife -->


    <string name="nightlife_1_name">Aristocrat Society Club</string>
    <string name="nightlife_1_description"></string>
    <string name="nightlife_1_website">www.club.club-aristocrat.ro</string>

    <string name="nightlife_2_name">Voynich Cafe &amp; Pub</string>
    <string name="nightlife_2_description"></string>
    <string name="nightlife_2_website">www.facebook.com/voynichcafe/</string>

    <string name="nightlife_3_name">Vintage Lounge</string>
    <string name="nightlife_3_description"></string>
    <string name="nightlife_3_website">www.sighisoaraonline.com/locatie/Vintage/85</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
